,text,spacy
125,"""@gustavocadile oscar winner actress anjelica huston just arrived to the red carpet @goldenglobes in @memekastudio"" genio amigo","[('anjelica huston', 'PERSON'), ('@memekastudio', 'GPE')]"
241,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
349,too busy for the this go around somebody tweet me if cumberbatch wins,[]
607,"lmao ""@morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('nbc', 'ORG')]"
619,"rt @morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('rt @morocca', 'PERSON'), ('nbc', 'ORG')]"
694,"you have won rt @nmadielson thought golden globes referred to @mzzhanson s nvm ""@vibemagazine n ",[]
780,@eonline @leodicaprio is just the best you look stunning again in the @goldenglobes hope u win tonight 2 thumbs up to you ,"[('@eonline @leodicaprio', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
819,"exactly ""@iheartheels lets consider mcqueen the winner and call it a night eh ",[]
832,rt @elitetravelkara lets hope for a kevin costner win for @slate9 ,"[('rt @elitetravelkara', 'PERSON'), ('kevin costner', 'PERSON')]"
836,rt @moderndestiny i really really really hope adele wins a globe tonight she looks gorg in @burberry @eredcarpet,[]
959,@taylorswift13 you look stunning at hope you win pretty,[]
976,"""@etcanada photo does bradley cooper go home a winner tonight oh hai ","[('@etcanada', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('hai', 'GPE')]"
1169,rt @thetennisphenom zooey deschanels bangs just won a golden globe ,"[('rt @thetennisphenom zooey', 'ORG')]"
1206,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
1246,"rt @suamivevu ""@gustavocadile oscar winner actress anjelica huston just arrived to the red carpet @goldenglobes in @memekastudio"" genio amigo","[('rt @suamivevu', 'PERSON'), ('anjelica huston', 'PERSON'), ('@memekastudio', 'GPE')]"
1270,rt @nydngossip denzel washington brought his daughter as his date if he doesnt win anything hes certainly getting father of the year,"[('rt @nydngossip', 'PERSON'), ('washington', 'GPE'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
1318,j lo for the win and the crowd goes wild stunning absolutely gorg ,[]
1325,who will win @taylorswift13 for or @officialadele for @goldenglobes @bootsandhearts,[]
1462,rt @possessionista if jennifer lawrence starts spinning around and her dress catches on fire she wins all the awards ,"[('rt @possessionista', 'PERSON'), ('jennifer lawrence', 'PERSON')]"
1466,rt @moderndestiny i really really really hope adele wins a globe tonight she looks gorg in @burberry @eredcarpet,[]
1491,rt @hollywoodlegacy golden globe classics on the red carpet of 1962 where she received an honorary award ,"[('rt @hollywoodlegacy golden globe classics', 'ORG'), ('1962', 'DATE')]"
1698,rt @soapnanny i want les miserables to win soooooo bad ,[]
1783,"rt @morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('rt @morocca', 'PERSON'), ('nbc', 'ORG')]"
1876,"rt @morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('rt @morocca', 'PERSON'), ('nbc', 'ORG')]"
1919,im happy if anne hathaway wins @goldenglobes,"[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
1967,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
2036,i feel bad for anne hathaway that shes going to win an oscar next month with that haircut ,"[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('next month', 'DATE')]"
2185,rt @theindiechicks what movie did you fall in love with that you hope wins their categories ,[]
2261,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
2263,rt @mimifabstar j lo for the win and the crowd goes wild stunning absolutely gorg ,"[('rt @mimifabstar', 'ORG')]"
2269,sofa vergara please win ,"[('sofa vergara', 'PERSON')]"
2296,"not sure how exciting the will be without taylor swifts ""omg i won"" act","[('taylor', 'PERSON')]"
2363,agreed rt @alexandrawrote hair dress makeup marion cottilard wins ,[]
2507,touche rt @wikimapper @franchambers golden globes is just a different kind of politics i for one hope argo wins,"[('touche rt @wikimapper @franchambers golden', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2826,hoping silver linings playbook wins it all tonight ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
2937,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
2944,id watch the but scripted tv wins out over awards shows every time ,[]
2956,rt @shtight86 i take it back from kathrine mcphee sofia vergara will always win best tits ,"[('kathrine mcphee', 'ORG')]"
2975,rt @awallenstein dear viewers dont tweet each winner as theyre named we can cut duplication in our feeds by oh 900,[]
3088,rt @vampirediariecw hoping silver linings playbook wins it all tonight ,"[('rt @vampirediariecw', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
3168,"rt @morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('rt @morocca', 'PERSON'), ('nbc', 'ORG')]"
3172,@piercefc and i have made our predictions and a bet for the i think im gonna win ,[]
3320,rt @thebrunetteone ben affleck you are hot i hope you win i hope kathryn bigelow wins too but i hope you win ,"[('ben affleck', 'PERSON'), ('kathryn', 'PERSON')]"
3385,rt @nathanfillion en route to golden globes hope i win ,[]
3406,rt @versace presenter oscar award winner halle berry is showstopping in a printed gown from atelier versace fall 2012 at the golden globes right now,"[('@versace', 'ORG'), ('berry', 'PERSON'), ('fall 2012', 'DATE')]"
3434,if they dont win stuff then the golden globes is getting a strong worded letter,[]
3453,are the golden globes tonight good luck to jessica lange and @mssarahpaulson @ahsfx deserves to win big,"[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('jessica', 'PERSON'), ('@mssarahpaulson', 'PERSON')]"
3476,which movies or tv shows do you hope to win big at the ,[]
3589,hugh jakman better win ,"[('hugh jakman', 'PERSON')]"
3608,if anne hathaway doesnt win best supporting actress i will literally get on a plane to la and stab helen hunt in the tit ,"[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
3653,well no matter the winners of the tonight the umpa loopas will be glad to know their family members won ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
3669,another win for the pats now the golden globes ,[]
3739,rt @versace presenter oscar award winner halle berry is showstopping in a printed gown from atelier versace fall 2012 at the golden globes right now,"[('@versace', 'ORG'), ('berry', 'PERSON'), ('fall 2012', 'DATE')]"
3758,"rt @jessetyler after seeing ""les miserables"" or as i like to call it ""omg its you again"" i am pulling for anne hathaway to win her award","[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
3824, victory and just in time for the golden globes,[]
3838,rt @spanxinc dont forget to include in your tweets for a chance to win brachacha and bravo2 fab bras to support your golden globes,"[('@spanxinc', 'ORG'), ('bravo2', 'GPE')]"
3857,rt @pimpbillclinton i just won the golden globe for acting like i give a shit about whatever my wife is talking about ,[]
3869,anne is wearing chanel you dont wear chanel unless you are seriously in it to win it if she doesnt win its a travesty ,[]
3943,zero dark thirty better win all the awards ,"[('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('thirty', 'CARDINAL')]"
3994,im usually alright at disguising my opinion on things but if anne hathaway doesnt win at the ill be superrrr grumpy,"[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
4111,rt @staypuft in 1985 ghostbusters was nominated for three golden globes we won none unforgivable,"[('1985', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
4191,i hope django unchained wins everything it wont ,[]
4205,@huffpoststyle anne hathaway hands down she should win an award for pulling off that chanel ,"[('@huffpoststyle anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
4221,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
4255,patriots win now its time,[]
4263,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
4282,"rt @lokay the first celeb to ask any member of the ""today"" show crew on the red carpet ""wheres ann curry"" wins my undying respect","[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
4302,now time for the nice win @patriots,[]
4447,excellent win now time for the ,[]
4452,rt @ericadelong dustin hoffman wins best personality on the red carpet tonight he is a presenter his movie opens jan 25th,"[('rt @ericadelong dustin hoffman', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('jan 25th', 'DATE')]"
4512,glad the patriots won since i spent the last 2 hours looking at bill belichicks short sleeve hoody instead of coverage,"[('the last 2 hours', 'TIME')]"
4651,rt @evaperez @huffpoststyle anne hathaway hands down she should win an award for pulling off that chanel ,"[('rt @evaperez @huffpoststyle anne', 'PERSON')]"
4737,"geniusss ""@anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ",[]
4824,rt @courtneybrg alright twitter newsfeed you win ill watch the ,"[('rt @courtneybrg', 'ORG')]"
4845,my final best dressed ranking winner mcphee second dockery third marguiles fourth hathaway and fifth swift ,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL')]"
4883,some actress is going to win a golden globe for best actress tonight and i havent washed my hair in 5 days i win ,"[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('5 days', 'DATE')]"
4885,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
4891,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
4944,hopefully the are good and that jennifer lawrence wins tonight,"[('jennifer lawrence', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
5000,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5045,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5077,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5155,rt @allofherclowes sorry midterms golden globes gets the win,[]
5193,this seems like a good time to remind you that the tourist was nominated for 3 golden globes whilst true grit received none ,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
5219,time for the golden globes part of me thinks it will be hilarious if the newsroom and smash win the hfpa always gives such gems,[]
5221,"""@patriots win next stop afc championship game"" it was a great game now on to the golden globes","[('afc', 'ORG')]"
5226,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5305, are actually about to start wins everything ever,[]
5440,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5575,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
5608,rt @adamrubins this seems like a good time to remind you that the tourist was nominated for 3 golden globes whilst true grit received none ,"[('rt @adamrubins', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
5741,now that the pats won i can watch the in peace hahahaa,[]
5749,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
5763,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
5774,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
5926, win now on to the ,[]
5939,andddd its time please let my daves win fingers crossed ,[]
5962,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
5966,bill murray wins ,"[('bill murray', 'PERSON')]"
5976,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6015,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6025,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6087,i love watching the golden globes i hope zero dark thirty wins something,"[('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
6106,with that shot bill murray wins for greatest beard of the night ,[]
6206,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6244,im just watching to see adele win an award ,[]
6253,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6275,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6337,bill murrays facial hair has already won the night ,"[('bill murrays', 'PERSON')]"
6368,rt @coffeecocktail i hope adele wins skyfall is the greatest song ,"[('rt @coffeecocktail', 'ORG')]"
6545,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
6596,pats win 1ds in africa doing charity stuff les mis is gonna sweep at the golden globes ,"[('1ds', 'ORDINAL'), ('africa', 'LOC')]"
6647,denzel better win ,[]
6654,i just want to see more benedict is that too much to ask oh and that he wins that would be da best ,[]
6785, red carpet winner so far michelle dockery from downton not so keen on kerry washington ,"[('downton', 'GPE'), ('washington', 'GPE')]"
6932,bill murray wins the beard award ,"[('bill murray', 'PERSON')]"
7002,bill murrays facial hair wins the golden globes,"[('bill murrays', 'PERSON')]"
7096,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7175,rt @cosmopolitan amy poehlers cleavage for the double win tonight ,"[('@cosmopolitan', 'GPE'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
7228,rt @musicforants bill murrays facial hair has already won the night ,[]
7268,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7269,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7291,bill fuckin murray is pulling a wolverine fuck yea he wins all the we the fuck they give away ,"[('bill fuckin murray', 'PERSON')]"
7376,tha golden globes are ontryn see django flight win somethin,"[('tha golden', 'PERSON')]"
7520,im sorry once upon a time the golden globes won,[]
7546,golden globes are on everything i like will not win,[]
7615,breaking bill murrays van buren wins all the golden globes,"[('bill murrays van buren', 'PERSON')]"
7644,pats won and the golden globes are on woooo,[]
7682,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7706,clooney and affleck sitting together fucking win ,[]
7903,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7921,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
7945,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
8032,rt @versace presenter oscar award winner halle berry is showstopping in a printed gown from atelier versace fall 2012 at the golden globes right now,"[('@versace', 'ORG'), ('berry', 'PERSON'), ('fall 2012', 'DATE')]"
8087,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
8125,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
8152,the begins hope django unchained wins an award in the name of the underdog,[]
8178,gonna check out the hoping django unchained and breaking bad win,[]
8180,im still mad at olivia munn for the @taylorswift13 episode but she wins my most wanted dress ,[]
8293,if leonardo dicaprio doesnt win anything i will be pissed ,[]
8368,rt @joannasimkin that james cameron joke win ,"[('rt @joannasimkin', 'ORG'), ('james cameron', 'PERSON')]"
8381,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
8716,i dont know why people would root for celebrities and movies in the because when they win what do you get think about it,[]
8820,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
8860,amy poehler just won the goodnight everybody,[]
8878,rt @joannasimkin that james cameron joke win ,"[('rt @joannasimkin', 'ORG'), ('james cameron', 'PERSON')]"
8924,amy poehler wins the night game over ,[]
8992,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
9154,here we go the 7oth @goldengl0bes starts n0w follow along f0r exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,[]
9262,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
9276,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
9374,and wins the night with her james cameron burn ,"[('james cameron burn', 'PERSON')]"
9432,watching cant wait to see who wins,[]
9536,for any tv show to win over watching the golden globes it has to be pretty dang good ,[]
9544,golden globes will ben affleck and katheryn bigelow have better luck after oscar snubs consolation wins for b ,"[('ben affleck', 'PERSON'), ('katheryn bigelow', 'PERSON')]"
9552,watching the golden globes i say silver linings wins best movie,[]
9695,tina fey and amy poehler for the win ,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
9722,tina and amy have won me over within the 5 minutes theyve been on stage ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('the 5 minutes', 'TIME')]"
9811,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
9877,agreed rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,"[('@perezhilton', 'GPE')]"
9977,my patriots won now time for the golden globes amy and tina are killing it,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
10066,"dear everyone livetweeting the ""blank just won"" is not engaging it is merely typing",[]
10071,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10082,im so anxious to see who wins ,[]
10088,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
10150,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
10257,so far tina fey wins best dressed im obsessed with that dress ,[]
10291,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10399,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
10505,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10528,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10531,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10539, and win the cutest couple award love k,[]
10586,if i ever win the powerball jackpot im buying tina fey and amy poehler first ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
10614,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10643,"rt @jessetyler after seeing ""les miserables"" or as i like to call it ""omg its you again"" i am pulling for anne hathaway to win her award","[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
10678,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10701,"rt @jessetyler after seeing ""les miserables"" or as i like to call it ""omg its you again"" i am pulling for anne hathaway to win her award","[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
10710,i dont even care who wins anymore i just want tina and amy to keep talking ,[]
10720,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10750,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
10868,@lenadunham please win it ,"[('@lenadunham', 'DATE')]"
11270,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
11320,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
11348,golden globes movie nominees who will win vs who should,[]
11356,good pats win on to the golden globes ,[]
11409,tina fey golden globes win,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
11434,rt @aleywormet for any tv show to win over watching the golden globes it has to be pretty dang good ,[]
11452,rt @proteautype bill murray wins best facial hair of the night and the 19th century ,"[('bill murray', 'PERSON'), ('the night and the 19th century', 'TIME')]"
11546,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
11638,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
11678, zooey deschanel lena dunham for the win please,[]
11734,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11747,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11758,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11759,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11761,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11765,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11766,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11767,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11769, golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn @suryaray @suryaray3,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11771,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11774,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11777,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11780,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11781,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11783,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11787,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11789,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11790,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11792,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11793,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11794,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11795,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11804,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11805,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11810,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11811,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11814,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11816,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11818,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11823,golden globes tv nominees who willshould win cnn ,"[('cnn', 'ORG')]"
11937,whos watching the and who do you want to win,[]
11969,rt @bwaydoc omg amy poehler and tina fey totally win ,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
12079,rt @nydngossip denzel washington brought his daughter as his date if he doesnt win anything hes certainly getting father of the year,"[('rt @nydngossip', 'PERSON'), ('washington', 'GPE'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
12127,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
12313,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
12451,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
12767,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
12836,"whoever makes a ringtone of amy singing ""i dream a dream"" wins my heart send it to me ",[]
12953,watching the golden globes with my parents we are keeping score on how many of our favorite nominees win ,[]
12997,"rt @akmcquade ""me too i used to win awards for that too"" tina fey to julianne moore on playing sarah palin ","[('julianne moore', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
13059,go leo please win ,[]
13216,leo needs to win for django ,"[('leo', 'ORG')]"
13232,what if leo won an award what if it happened ,[]
13293,rt @spanxinc dont forget to include in your tweets for a chance to win brachacha and bravo2 fab bras to support your golden globes,"[('@spanxinc', 'ORG'), ('bravo2', 'GPE')]"
13436,daniel daylewis should win an oscar for that et finger point ,"[('daniel daylewis', 'ORG')]"
13480,leo better win ,[]
13487,i dont even care about who wins give me more tina and amy ,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
13495,leo i hope you win everything ,[]
13555,i did want christoph waltz to win he was awesome in django unchained ,[]
13571,i dont really care about who actually wins the awards ,[]
13594,the real winner of the golden globes is apparently sideboob,[]
13610,if my nigga daniel craig wins something at the golden globes tonite,"[('daniel craig', 'PERSON')]"
13640,do guys watch the golden globes bourne ultimatum on tnt for the win,[]
13728,tommy lee jones mis respectos como actor pero echate cemento blanco en esa cara won ,"[('tommy lee jones mis', 'PERSON'), ('como', 'ORG'), ('blanco', 'GPE'), ('esa cara', 'PERSON')]"
13775,if any of these supporting actors win its going to be an unbearable night ,"[('an unbearable night', 'TIME')]"
13777,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
13799,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
13802,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
13831,and the winner isleo nope sorry ,[]
13836,"rt @morocca hey nbc shouldve gotten a ""mani cam"" e wins this round ","[('rt @morocca', 'PERSON'), ('nbc', 'ORG')]"
13840,django won its first award ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
13850,yes christoph waltz won he was soo soo good in django ,[]
13865,django with a win play the rick ross ,"[('rick ross', 'PERSON')]"
13871,poooor leo he knows hes not going to win and looks so sad ,[]
13902,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
13955,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
13962,i want argo to win lots of things ,[]
13973,django wins ,[]
13977,big ups to walts on the win ,[]
13993,i wanted tommy lee jones to win ,"[('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
14011,wtf golden globes leo should have won,[]
14037,yayyyyy christoph wins best supporting actor thats one for django ,"[('yayyyyy christoph wins', 'PERSON')]"
14038, wins ,[]
14054,waltz won that was unexpected ,[]
14057,waltz for the win ,[]
14065,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
14074,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
14078,christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
14090,god damn thats a strong group of best supporting actors but waltz wins,[]
14104,can leo win something ,[]
14206,damn it will leo ever win anything ,[]
14209,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
14241,he won omg omg omg christoph is the best ahhhhhh so happy ,[]
14243,leo should have won ,[]
14247,the guy from inglorious bastards won a globe awesome ,[]
14254,christoph waltz wins for django ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
14264,i knew he would win he was fantastic in django ,[]
14323,ahhh leonardo shoulda won for django ,"[('ahhh leonardo shoulda', 'PERSON')]"
14335,omg christoph waltz looks so different with his short hair im glad he won ,[]
14338,i approve of this win ,[]
14355,christopher waltz won yes ,"[('christopher waltz', 'PERSON')]"
14368,christoph waltz for the win yes ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
14369,rack em up i predicted a win for christoph tonight well deserved ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
14380,django unchained is gonna win big tonight congrats ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
14418,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
14429,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
14439,called it christoph waltz wins best supporting ,[]
14444,first win for sorry leo again,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
14449,django unchained with the 1st win,"[('1st', 'ORDINAL')]"
14475,rt @mkpinbrooklyn i dont want anyone to win anything for django because i am an intolerant baseless tarantino hater ,[]
14499,rt @filmdotcom christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,[]
14514,rt @strongurgetofly i just want django unchained to win in every way possible ,[]
14548,django is gonna win so many golden globes,[]
14560,watching the golden globes can jlaw please win ,[]
14576,tommy lee jones should win the oscar though ,"[('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
14592,i want christoph waltz to win everything ,[]
14595,my leo didnt win ,[]
14611,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
14623,first django win of the night ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
14643,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
14697,and the first win of the night christoph waltz supporting actor django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
14722,first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
14723,django first win ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
14724,christoph waltz won i so knew he would win ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
14729,yay christoph waltz should win all the things ,[]
14738,there had better be some wins tonight for les mis ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
14757,christoph walz with the first win of the night ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
14813,really golden globes couldnt let leo win really,[]
14824,the golden globes the academy is all old white guys guess whos gonna win most if the awards old white guys,[]
14895,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
14900,bill murrays beard should win an award tonight ,"[('bill murrays beard', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
14904,rt @vulture first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
14922,christoph waltz is a pretty damn good actor but i wanted leo win ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
14958,"blm ntn but make sense ""@thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ",[]
14977,@leodicaprio should have won wtf ugh 3 hes so beautiful ,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
14986,golden globes movie nominees who will win vs who should ,[]
15000,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
15010,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
15039,django already won an award at the golden globes spike lee just kicked his tv,"[('lee', 'PERSON')]"
15046,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
15057,@heatherbarmore someone i dont know won an award for movie i dont know ,[]
15069,rt @seattlegeekly mandy patinkins beard should win all the awards ,[]
15086,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15103,mmm leo should win everything @goldenglobes,[]
15105,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
15113,christoph waltz should win the oscar too ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
15117,rt @beautylogicblog i knew he would win he was fantastic in django ,[]
15132,so excited that christoph waltz won best supporting actor he is amazing 3 ,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
15143,damn i was really hoping alan arkin would win for he was fantastic ,"[('alan', 'PERSON')]"
15161, christopher waltz wins best supporting actor ,"[('christopher', 'PERSON')]"
15164,supporting actor christoph waltz won yeaaaaaaahhhh @p3rladavid jajajaja una buena,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('buena', 'GPE')]"
15172,christoph waltz wins for django unchained @mikeandbilly ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
15203,django wins its first award ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15210,woah christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained i was between leo and hoffman ,[]
15233,if benedict cumberbatch wins his category no matter what else happens this year will be okay ,"[('this year', 'DATE')]"
15234,when is leo going to win an award ,[]
15257,did not pick him to win throwing off my picks right from the beginning ,[]
15259,dicaprio just cant catch a win it must be so hard to be that guy always being held down by the man ,[]
15279,rt @vulture first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
15287,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15298,very nice very well deserved award for christoph waltz as best supporting actor should win it again in a few months ,"[('a few months', 'DATE')]"
15320,my first pick wins chistoph waltz ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15346,"wahwanted tommy lee jones to win best supporting actorbut then i havent seen ""django"" ","[('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
15374,agreed amy and tina for the win rt @lindsaynk9 these opening jokes are amazing ,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
15392,samuel l jackson shouldve been nominated and shouldve won ,"[('samuel l jackson', 'PERSON')]"
15393,rt @fredasflicks takes the first win at the ,"[('@fredasflicks', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15394,christoph waltz wins the first award of the night dont need to watch the anymore then,"[('christoph', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15395,best supporting actor motion picture golden globe winner christoph waltz ,[]
15412,rt @yusufyuie just won a ,"[('rt @yusufyuie', 'PERSON')]"
15414,christoph waltz won @beeinnvee @jaseistheman ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15441,poor he only wins victorias secret models ,[]
15461,and the winner is christoph waltz,[]
15465,yay christoph loved him in django winner best supporting actor ,[]
15502,yes dr shultz sp won ,"[('dr shultz', 'PERSON')]"
15559,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
15566,yes 1 for 1 walz wins i got this ,"[('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
15583,daniel day lewis wins all the for his et performance,"[('daniel day', 'PERSON')]"
15594,christoph waltz wins the first bit of hardware and its well deserved ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15599,this is waltzs second golden globe both for quentin tarantino movies he also won in 2010 for inglourious basterds ,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('2010', 'DATE')]"
15618,"first award christoph waltz wins the for best supporting actor in ""django unchained""","[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15630,winner actor supporting role in motion picture christoph waltz ,[]
15631,wow christoph waltz wins best supporting actor did not think that was gonna happen ,[]
15640,django takes first win of the night with christoph waltz ,"[('django', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the night', 'TIME')]"
15677,django unchained for the first win im going to have to see this ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
15681,ayyyyyyye theyre playing @johnlegends song whenever django wins ,[]
15693,surprising win for django unchained ,[]
15708,christoph waltz should win another award for that accent ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
15716,rt @vulture first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
15727,rt @strongurgetofly i just want django unchained to win in every way possible ,[]
15760,fuck yess christoph waltz wins best supporting actor ,[]
15781,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
15783,im so glad christoph waltz won love him ,[]
15786,rt @alotofnothing i hope leo dicaprio wins so he can go on stage and make out with bradley cooper thats how it works right ,"[('rt @alotofnothing', 'PERSON')]"
15805,christoph waltz won best supporting actor in a motion picture for django unchained yes he did a great job,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15809,rt @clairescatter oh my word tina fey and amy poehler just won they just won the whole world ,"[('rt @clairescatter', 'PERSON')]"
15843,"rt @lcjreviews christoph waltz with the surprise win start to @goldenglobes a ""django"" night","[('@lcjreviews', 'ORG'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
15862,christophe waltz for the win so happy ,"[('christophe', 'ORG')]"
15864,@mikesavacool christophe waltz just won best supporting actor at the for ,"[('@mikesavacool christophe', 'ORG')]"
15873,yes christoph won for best supporting actor in ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
15881,the best actor alive wins the first award a damn good start to the evening ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('evening', 'TIME')]"
15895,rt @brentcbowers2 i want christoph waltz to win everything ,"[('rt @brentcbowers2', 'PERSON')]"
15925,christoph waltz wins best suppporting actor my favorite o,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15927,let the guy with the accent win again because hes funny to listen to ,[]
15931,you would think after 70 years of this they would have a better way for the winners to get to the stage once they win ,"[('70 years', 'DATE')]"
15964, starting off with a win for christolph waltz ,[]
15966,christoph waltz wins supporting actor i picked his django costar leo dicaprio 01 ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('01', 'CARDINAL')]"
15977,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for his role in django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15978,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
15979,i agree with this message rt @digitalgurl djanjo wins ,[]
16001,"rt @abc7newsbayarea christoph waltz has won best supporting actor for his work in quentin tarantinos ""django unchained""","[('rt @abc7newsbayarea christoph', 'PERSON')]"
16005,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
16013,"waltz they ""couldnt resist"" first is a perfect win","[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
16022,who the fuck is this guy fuck leo im glad he didnt win ,[]
16025,christoph waltz leo dicaprio are two of my fav actors glad one of them won ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
16032,rt @greatlyvalued django going to win a lot golden globes tonightand they deserve each one,[]
16079,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
16080,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
16091,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
16140,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
16149,"leo dicaprio shouldve won for ""django unchained"" but ill take christoph waltz ",[]
16171,christopher waltz wins best supporting actor havent seen django yet but i can already guarantee this is definitely deserved ,"[('christopher waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16196,leonardo dicaprio is the susan lucci of award shows oh wait she actually won something ,"[('leonardo dicaprio', 'PERSON')]"
16197,i hope leo knows hes always a winner in my heart always ,[]
16212,"""@emlundblad daniel day lewis wins all the for his et performance"" for shizzle",[]
16214,christoph waltz wins an award its more fun to say when you germanize the ws into vs ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
16215,rt @vulture first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
16220,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
16232,havent seen django yet but am happy christoph waltz wins supporting actor he was so good in previous tarantino film ,[]
16254,also can they just let my bb leo win something already ,[]
16263,cristoph waltz wins best supporting actor really enjoyed his performance in django unchained he deserves it ,[]
16296,christoph waltz admittedly the best thing about django unchained but his win seems odd ,"[('christoph', 'ORG')]"
16314,rt @impossiblemovie were rooting for naomi watts at tonights @goldenglobes retweet if you think she deserves to win for her performance in ,"[('watts', 'LOC')]"
16320,leo is still a winner in my heart ,"[('leo', 'ORG')]"
16325,rt @brandnewskies if benedict cumberbatch wins his category no matter what else happens this year will be okay ,"[('this year', 'DATE')]"
16333,when will dicaprio win ,[]
16341,christoph waltz carried django unchained glad to see him win ,[]
16349,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
16357,christoph waltz won best supporting actor for django unchained he deserved it ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16364,"christoph waltz wins best supporting actor motion picture for his work in ""django unchained"" ","[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16365,christoph waltz won a golden globe for best supporting actor in a motion picture congrats ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16366,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
16372,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
16380,christoph waltz wins the award for the horrible acceptance speech ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
16397,well deserved rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,[]
16402,"how many foreigners will win tonight with the hfpa in charge the answer is likely ""all of them""","[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
16403,christoph waltz wins the first award hes the only nominee i cared about he deserved it ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
16450,rt @tvwithoutpity our djaws just dropped wasnt expecting to win by a long shot leo was better but well take it ,[]
16484,christoph won ,"[('christoph', 'PERSON')]"
16486,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
16498,"yayyy ""django unchained"" my prediction is it will win most awards nominated for ",[]
16541,big win for ,[]
16548,les miserables better win a fucking award ,[]
16568,rt @vibemagazine go starting off with a string win ,[]
16589,i love christoph waltz so much he should win everything ,[]
16613,"now that someones won an award for it i need to stop saying ""that djarjeeling tea movie or whatever it is"" ",[]
16617,"i hope she wins rt ""@thehoborg just showed jennifer shes wearing a jacket she must be extra cold with that flu ",[]
16628,"""@washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ",[]
16642,rt @areeves11 django is going to win everything tonight and im ok with that ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
16653,sad alan arkin didnt win but thrilled to see christoph waltz on stage nothing like a noble bounty hunter ,"[('alan arkin', 'PERSON')]"
16670,christopher waltz won for django he deserved it ,"[('christopher waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16719,christoph waltz will win any award he is nominated for ever fact ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16733,"""@washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained niceeee",[]
16767,maggie smith wins tv supporting actress ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
16780,he was amazing but i just want to win rt @freshchrislaw christoph killed it tho,[]
16807,rt @iamaprildaniels django unchained wins it congrats christoph waltz ,[]
16835,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
16887,anyway can someone tell me if taylor wins her golden globes im in a cab atm ,"[('taylor', 'PERSON')]"
16888,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
16889,cuddled in blankets and watching the golden globes a week ago i wrote down my choices for who i think will win ill let you know how i do,"[('a week ago', 'DATE')]"
16919,doesnt christoph waltz win an award for everything tarantino puts him in ,[]
16935,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
16938,maggie smith for the win ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
16943,the winner for best supporting tv actress is maggie smith,[]
16952,dont know much about tv wins i just do the watching ,[]
16958,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
16970,sarah paulson should win all the awards just for american horror story ,"[('sarah paulson', 'PERSON'), ('american', 'NORP')]"
17015,i dont want lincoln to win anything all night ,"[('lincoln', 'ORG')]"
17038,dowager wins ,[]
17060,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
17109,poor leo i dont think hell ever win a golden globe maybe one day leo ,"[('one day', 'DATE')]"
17129,of course maggie smith won queen ,"[('smith', 'PERSON')]"
17133,yay modern family didnt win ,[]
17168,my greataunt maggie wins again ,[]
17192,connie brittons hair for all the wins ,[]
17193,downton abbey for the win yay maggie ,"[('downton abbey', 'PERSON')]"
17202,you cant win against maggie smith ,[]
17208,there should be an award for best host if tina fey amy poehler didnt win id scream bloody murder,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
17214,"""take off an article of clothing any time maggie smith wins"" and so ",[]
17222,maggie smith won dddd ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17258,"they actually said ""downton abbey season 2"" odd oh well maggie won ","[('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
17285,sofia vergara looks amazing too bad she never wins ,[]
17290,dowager countess wins ,[]
17315,maggie smith with the win shocker ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17334,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
17344,yay won ,[]
17356, wins the first award of the night ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
17358,rt @radiotj christoph waltz wins first award well deserved love that guy,"[('rt @radiotj christoph', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
17385,rt @amandafennelly i wonder if christophs great win is a sign of some more surprises to come ,[]
17424,maggie smith win go downton ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
17445,maggie smith for the win ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17448,aw yeah maggie smith wins @thedowagershat,[]
17458,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
17466,maggie smith always wins every award ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17467,rt @rollingout yes christoph waltz wins for django unchained ,[]
17541,yes maggie smith won hahah ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17552,ahhh maggie smith won dor downton abbey she is so great ,"[('ahhh maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('dor downton', 'PERSON')]"
17560,downton abby for the win maggie smith make that show ,"[('downton abby', 'PERSON')]"
17588,dame maggie smith wins of course for downton abbey ,"[('downton', 'GPE')]"
17594,rt @anagasteyer im going to be so pissed if laura linney doesnt win for ,"[('rt @anagasteyer', 'PERSON')]"
17609,maggie smith should win every time she is nominated ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17612,dame maggie smith for the win again she is the coolest ,[]
17622,sofia should just win everything period ,[]
17624,rt @pagesix first awardchristoph waltz wins best supporting actor for motion picture ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
17627,maggie smith won for ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17672,rt @mrbateslegal maggie smith wins ,[]
17690,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
17705,wait just a minute you dont have to be present to win at the golden globes,"[('just a minute', 'TIME')]"
17716,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
17722,"k if you arent able to ""make it"" to the golden globes and you get an award you shouldnt be able to receive it",[]
17733,"rt @thr christoph waltz wins the for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr christoph', 'ORG')]"
17747,i wish more people that won werent there to accept lets make this years golden globes 15 minutes and move on,"[('this years', 'DATE'), ('15 minutes', 'TIME')]"
17749,maggie smith won for best tv actressi think she won for being smart enough to skip the golden globes,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17750,"rt @thr maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting actress tv for ""downton abbey"" ","[('rt @thr maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17751,yay maggie smith won cant wait to watch downton abey afer the golden globes,"[('yay maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('downton abey', 'PERSON')]"
17755,les mis bette win like 70000 golden globes or i swear,"[('70000', 'CARDINAL')]"
17818,so happy waltz won for best supporting actor definitely most deserved ,[]
17821,first win of the night ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
17828,maggie smith wins for best supporting actress in a drama go professor mcgonnagall ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
17855,wuzzup maggie smith too posh to hang at the yay for a win,[]
17874, boooo i wanted @sofiavergara to win,"[('@sofiavergara', 'GPE')]"
17891,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
17899,new award show rule if you cannot attend you are not eligible to win ,[]
17901,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
17911,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
17913,"djangos first win at the operation ""spike are you okay youre not breathing""begins","[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
17940,when people i dont know win awards and are not there to except and give a speech i could careless about it makes kinda happy ,[]
18010,"rt @fashionweeknyc christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('rt @fashionweeknyc christoph', 'ORG')]"
18022,love the winner of best support actor in movies he s wonderful ,[]
18052,rt @mrbobbybones christoph waltz carried django unchained glad to see him win ,[]
18053,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18060,thank god christoph waltz won best supporting actor in a motion picture ,[]
18072,rt @iamaprildaniels django unchained wins it congrats christoph waltz ,[]
18088,maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a miniseries for downton abbey ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
18104,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18115,booo @haydenpanettier should have won ,[]
18158,professor mcgonagall just won a golden globe ,[]
18163,christoph waltz win for django woot ,[]
18211,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18214,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
18232,win for love that show ,[]
18241,maggie smith yay of course the dowager countess was going to win ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
18248,maggie smith wins a ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
18255,mentally preparing myself for the bunch of win that will be @scottishguys tweets a wonderful readalong companion to the ,[]
18279,rt @vibemagazine go starting off with a string win ,[]
18287,i dont care how many golden globes it wins im still choosing to treat downton abbey as a fictional parody of a bbc show,"[('bbc', 'ORG')]"
18298,amy tina win they just win the golden globes,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
18369,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
18385,ok maggie won im happy ,[]
18402,rt @proncis i did this joke last year but gryffindor gets 150 house points for that win from maggie smith ,"[('rt @proncis', 'PERSON'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('150', 'CARDINAL')]"
18412,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18418,quentin tarantino has helped christoph waltz win two and an academy award those two need to keep working together,"[('quentin tarantino', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
18431,if les miz and anyone associated with it doesnt win everything its nominated for i will shit bricks ,[]
18442,rt @vibemagazine go starting off with a string win ,[]
18465,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18476,heres marilyn at the 1960s golden globe awards she won best actress in a musical for some like it hot ,"[('1960s', 'DATE')]"
18479,"rt @fuggirls maggie smith was like ""eh i wont come the supporting actor winner needs more time to talk"" h ","[('rt @fuggirls maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
18490,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18498,sorry hubby didnt win but shes still a winner to him ,[]
18545,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18549,rt @hulu maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a miniseries for downton abbey ,"[('rt @hulu', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
18557,rt @tinselkorey @sofiavergara won in my books ,"[('rt @tinselkorey @sofiavergara', 'PERSON')]"
18568,rt @rulesforbelles is anyoneeee surprised the glorious maggie smith won that nope ,"[('rt @rulesforbelles', 'PERSON')]"
18570,maggie smith is clearly above attending the golden globes but im still glad she won ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
18587,i believe in you leoone day you will win ,[]
18590,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18593,rt @muneversleeps spoiler alert leo dicaprio will receive zero rewards for anything he ever does in any movie because life is unfair ,"[('@muneversleeps', 'CARDINAL'), ('alert leo', 'PERSON'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
18618,so glad christoph waltz won if you havent seen django unchained i strongly recommend it ,[]
18630,when leonardo dicaprio finally wins something the world and myself will be shedding long overdue tears of happiness ,[]
18646,yeah won bst supporting for my choice too ,[]
18703,how did hayden not win for ,[]
18709,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18731,supporting actress dramaminiseries my guess maggie smith downton actual win lady grantham ,"[('smith downton', 'ORG')]"
18734,dame maggie smith won again yay ,[]
18754,"""@masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for first win for ","[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
18766,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
18792,maggie smith won at the ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
18806,like obvi maggie wins and she doesnt even have to be there @goldenglobes,[]
18807,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
18849,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
18860,if waltz won fritz wins by the transitive property ,"[('won fritz', 'PERSON')]"
18899,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18913,unlike other awards in the the celebrities only go to eat and do not win awards ,[]
18929,i want @sofiavergada to win just to hear her speaklove her ,[]
18931,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18940,best intro of a the ladies killed it glad to see maggie smith win ,"[('best intro', 'PERSON')]"
18956,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
18957, ahhhh leo didnt won ,[]
18962,i hope jared leto wins best director ,[]
18974, winner of best imitation of a college football teamnorte dame,[]
18997,mcgonagall from won a oh wait my bad abbey,[]
19024,rt @mrbateslegal maggie smith wins ,[]
19029,rt @ctboom you should not be allowed to win an award if you cant be thereor if you are on downton abbey ,[]
19030,id have loved to see leo to win best supporting actor but im equally happy for waltz ,[]
19039,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19055,poor leo didnt win christoph waltz did deserve it as much as him though ,[]
19066,someone poke @pattonoswalt and tell him we need a dowager countess wins an award joke stat ,[]
19086,@downtonabbey maggie smith wins again congratulations ,"[('@downtonabbey', 'ORG'), ('smith', 'PERSON')]"
19093,maggie smith wins this starts so well ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
19140,well clearly the woman with the best didnt win too bad @sofiavergara but i think youre fabulous on ,[]
19147,jon bon jovi is gonna win ,"[('jon bon', 'PERSON')]"
19149,rt @washingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for unchained ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
19167,rt @ggarlock guys i just won all the golden globes i want to thank no one,[]
19169,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19175,maggie smith wins the for downton abbey well done wishing her great health and many more awards ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('the for', 'ORG')]"
19187,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19232,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19234,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19248,maggie smith wins at the for switching to in 46 minutes to continue the celebration ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('46 minutes', 'TIME')]"
19251,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19254,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19286,"""@jjonz100 maggie smith didnt think shed win so shes at chuck e cheese"" no @theladygrantham is at downton arbys ","[('chuck', 'PERSON'), ('@theladygrantham', 'ORG'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
19294,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19308,dowager countess for the win ,[]
19312,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
19333,"""@rachelgeb must be present to win like any good firemens auxiliary auction",[]
19338,"""@masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for @downtonabbey","[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG'), ('@downtonabbey', 'ORG')]"
19365,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor in django unchainedmaggie smith wins best supporting tv actress in downton abbey,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('django', 'GPE'), ('smith', 'GPE'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
19377,@goldenglobes christoph waltz and maggie smith kick the night off with best supporting actoractress wins ,"[('smith kick the night', 'PERSON')]"
19388,rt @hecklerforever was it just me or did @goldenglobes tweet the winner seconds before it was even announced ,"[('seconds', 'TIME')]"
19410,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19418,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19426,we new maggie smith was gonna win but id be happy with it in hands too ,[]
19427,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
19445,always bet on the dowager countess always maggie smith wins but isnt there to accept baller ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
19471,@goldenglobes why never leonardo he should win for all the great movies hes made great,[]
19473,rt @elvisduranshow maggie smith from downtown abbey gets the win for best support actress in tv movie series or miniseries ,"[('rt @elvisduranshow', 'PERSON')]"
19510,but seriously alan arkin or tommy lee jones shouldve won they delivered amazing performances ,"[('alan', 'PERSON'), ('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
19519,rt @angelaeloise christoph waltz was the best part of django unchained so glad he won ,[]
19577,"""@trinifood oh my word @kerrywashington at the golden globes win"" yes and yes",[]
19587,"faith in humanity rt @thr maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting actress tv for ""downton abbey"" ","[('smith', 'PERSON')]"
19593,golden globes im literally gonna cry every time les mis wins ,[]
19597, just won yay so start getting ,[]
19644,rt @movieline christoph waltz wins the golden globe for django unchained ,"[('@movieline', 'ORG')]"
19670,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19708,rt @azcentral tonights 1st winner christoph waltz for his supporting role in django ,"[('1st', 'ORDINAL')]"
19749,the lovely maggie smith wins for downton ,"[('downton', 'GPE')]"
19750,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19776,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
19778,patriots win now on to the loving tina amy,"[('tina', 'GPE')]"
19783,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
19787,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
19791,well maggie smith won which means im not wearing socks ,[]
19812,so glad christoph waltz won a best supporting actor for django unchained he was awesome ,[]
19815,rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'PERSON')]"
19824,rt @thetimes maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting actress tv for her role in downton abbey ,"[('rt @thetimes', 'ORG'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
19827,if nominees arent present they do not deserve to win ,[]
19831,was hoping tommy lee jones would have won best supporting actor ,"[('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
19865,yay maggie smith won ,"[('yay maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
19869,rt @mikesisak best supporting actor should win leonardo dicaprio will win tommy lee jones did win christoph waltz ,"[('tommy lee jones', 'PERSON')]"
19887,rt @elvisduranshow maggie smith from downtown abbey gets the win for best support actress in tv movie series or miniseries ,"[('rt @elvisduranshow', 'PERSON')]"
19889,i hate the but as long as the movie wins big ill be happy,[]
19897,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
19917,poor leo i really hope he wins something someday ,[]
19929,girls for the win rt @girlshbo and the are on at the same time tonight ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
19933,rt @tmagazine django unchained was incredible and mr waltz deserves every accolade he receives bravo ,[]
19936,in my mind sarah paulson won that globe we should take all the awards and give them to sarah paulson ,"[('sarah paulson', 'PERSON'), ('sarah paulson', 'PERSON')]"
19937,rt @chaddukes christoph waltz should win everything every year @goldenglobes,"[('rt @chaddukes christoph', 'ORG'), ('every year', 'DATE')]"
19945,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
19947,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
19959,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
20023,rt @theatlanticwire maggie smith wins supporting actress foreigners living in america give award to foreigner who wont travel to america ,"[('america', 'GPE'), ('america', 'GPE')]"
20036,rt @gbprobst the golden globes are off to a good start tina fey and amy poehler were funny and charming christoph waltz wins a well deserved award,"[('rt @gbprobst', 'PERSON'), ('tina', 'GPE')]"
20065,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
20080,rt @muneversleeps spoiler alert leo dicaprio will receive zero rewards for anything he ever does in any movie because life is unfair ,"[('@muneversleeps', 'CARDINAL'), ('alert leo', 'PERSON'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
20083,rt @qtarchives and the winner is christoph waltz django unchained ,[]
20101,congratumaleyshions to professor mcgonagall winner teh ang pagbuhay mo sa hugwarts group hugz mwahmwahtsutsup ,"[('teh ang pagbuhay', 'PERSON'), ('sa hugwarts', 'ORG'), ('hugz mwahmwahtsutsup', 'PERSON')]"
20106,i really just hope silver linings playbook wins something ,[]
20116,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
20123,i wanted or to win im lying i wanted them both to win they were both amazing both deserving ,[]
20126,rt @thetimes maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting actress tv for her role in downton abbey ,"[('rt @thetimes', 'ORG'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
20128,amy tina for the win these girls are on fire ,"[('amy tina', 'ORG')]"
20134,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
20163,"rt @jessetyler after seeing ""les miserables"" or as i like to call it ""omg its you again"" i am pulling for anne hathaway to win her award","[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON')]"
20168,rt @yale kudos to alumna meryl streep 75mfa mostnominated awarded performer to all tonights nominees,"[('alumna meryl', 'PERSON')]"
20172,rt @muneversleeps spoiler alert leo dicaprio will receive zero rewards for anything he ever does in any movie because life is unfair ,"[('@muneversleeps', 'CARDINAL'), ('alert leo', 'PERSON'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
20198,christoph waltzs reaction to when foxx asks him if hes really a dentist should win him every award ,[]
20221,rt @azcentral tonights 1st winner christoph waltz for his supporting role in django ,"[('1st', 'ORDINAL')]"
20227,seriously rt @shewired can we just give dame maggie a lifetime achievement award already let somebody else win tg ,[]
20232,"rt @imkristenbell here here ""@daxshepard1 in the unlikely event cooper doesnt win i hope security has a plan in place ","[('rt @imkristenbell', 'PERSON')]"
20248, wins wont host next year ,"[('next year', 'DATE')]"
20249,the early verdict is in and amy poehler and tina fey have already won 2013 ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('2013', 'DATE')]"
20262, maggie smith won supporting actress for abbey,[]
20271,rt @vulture first winner of the night christoph waltz for django unchained ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
20272,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
20314,rt @gcdb he wins congratulations to christoph ,"[('rt @gcdb', 'PERSON')]"
20384,@girlshbo but the golden globes are on too watch you guys win awards or watch the award nominated show itself ,[]
20451,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
20493,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
20575,maggie smith wins best supporting actress and im 1for1 a pretty obvious pick though so im not getting cocky yet ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('1for1', 'DATE')]"
20590,rt @brendonwalsh katherine bigelow wins the leni riefenstahl award for excellence in propaganda ,[]
20610,did leonardo dicaprio win oh well then fuck all of you ,[]
20621,"""@masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for d give her all the golden globes","[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
20635,@crystaleyesed did she win anything not watchin ,[]
20660,@lenadunham is fucking adorable great look for her good job hope you win tonight ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
20662,daniel daylewis better win best actor ,"[('daniel daylewis', 'ORG')]"
20672,poor leo hes never going to win anything is he ,[]
20693,breaking bad better win something tonight ,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
20714,watching the @goldenglobes makes me think of the @grammys imagining the day when @asilentfilm wins one @altnation,"[('the day', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
20722,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
20726, wins the for best supporting actress my award for being the coolest woman on the planet ,[]
20746,rt @stephaniekettle sofia should have won ,[]
20755,its too bad leo couldnt have somehow also won too ,[]
20767,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
20773,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
20774,maggie smiths win makes me really mad the are on at the same time as downton abbey,"[('downton', 'GPE')]"
20778,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
20797,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
20816,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
20819,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
20822,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
20863,maggie smith will always win always ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
20890,"rt @elprofe316 djangos first win at the operation ""spike are you okay youre not breathing""begins","[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
20891,well at least the best thing in won at go ,[]
20903,leonardo dicaprio should just win an award for being nominated the most but never wins ,[]
20906,"""@pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for love her new episode tonight","[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
20910,christoph waltz was great still hoped leonardo dicaprio wouldve won ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
20923,rt @thirteenny congratulations to maggie smith on your win ,"[('rt @thirteenny congratulations', 'ORG')]"
20930,rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'PERSON')]"
20954,first drink of the game if maggie smith wins i dont even know who she is but she won within minutes and i drank ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('minutes', 'TIME')]"
20963,and the german won,"[('german', 'NORP')]"
20978,rt @perezhilton amy poehler for the win ,[]
20995,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
21008,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
21038,rt @higginator watching the golden globes i hope leonardo wins aomething,[]
21071,im okay with hollywood when two 40ish funny women host the golden globes and one elderlyish funny woman wins the first award,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
21130,maggie smith won for something not sure drinking and typing ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
21141,voters dont understand that sofia vergara will give you the best speech in the history of speeches if she wins let her win ,[]
21151,she may not have won but sofia vergara still has that pepsi contract lauging all the way to the bank ,"[('pepsi', 'ORG')]"
21155,maggie smith reacts to her win ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON')]"
21167,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
21171,rt @colestratton the dowager countess wins a golden globe but the earl of grantham already lost it in a bad investment ,"[('rt @colestratton', 'ORG')]"
21253,rt @eliyudin the real winner of the golden globes is apparently sideboob,"[('rt @eliyudin', 'PERSON')]"
21350,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django @unchainedmovie ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON')]"
21352,of course granmamma won ,"[('granmamma', 'PERSON')]"
21376,i wanted dicaprio to win but waltz deserves it none the less ,[]
21393,rt @johnnyfocal maggie smith wins for @goldenglobes,"[('rt @johnnyfocal', 'ORG')]"
21411,"rt @fashionweeknyc maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting actress tv for ""downton abbey"" ","[('rt @fashionweeknyc', 'ORG'), ('smith', 'GPE')]"
21433,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
21462,it doesnt really matter who wins does it does it ,[]
21465,rt @ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj,"[('@ap', 'ORG')]"
21479, wins best supporting actor for django unchained he was incredible @norbuck,[]
21501,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
21525,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
21608,and the winner for best miniseries or tv movie goes to game change ,[]
21627,i hope the hour wins best miniseries ,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]"
21631,rt @theweek maggie smith the dowager countess wins best supporting actress for tv performance for downton abbey ,"[('@theweek', 'DATE'), ('smith the dowager', 'ORG'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
21664,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
21710,christophe waltz and maggie smith just won golden globes,"[('christophe', 'ORG')]"
21759," rt @thr christoph waltz wins the golden globe for best supporting actor in ""django unchained"" ","[('@thr', 'ORG')]"
21787,"golden globes winner for best supporting actor in a motion picture is christoph waltz for ""django unchained""",[]
21790,christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at the golden globes 2013 ,"[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('2013', 'DATE')]"
21795,"christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at the golden globes 2013 pimg src"" ","[('christoph waltz', 'PERSON'), ('the golden globes', 'FAC')]"
21801, wins best miniseries or tv movie ,[]
21828,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
21847,rt @brendonwalsh katherine bigelow wins the leni riefenstahl award for excellence in propaganda ,[]
21862,just tell me when wins @ahsfx,[]
21886,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
21888,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
21893,im sorry hatfields mccoys should have won ,[]
21904,golden globes 2013 game change hbo wins best miniseries or tv movie,"[('2013', 'CARDINAL')]"
21947,political animals should have won ,[]
21958,anyhow the winner is game change apparently its about the us electoral process i think ,"[('us', 'GPE')]"
21970,the girl should have won ,[]
21971,yes yes ye game change won ,[]
21975,oh snooze sarah palin wins i wonder how she feels,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
22001,"""@nyminutemag is leo dicaprio ever going to win won for best actor drama 4 the departed","[('@nyminutemag', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
22027,game change wins best miniseries or tv movie ,[]
22031,i knew game change would win effing fantastic movie even if it did only cover half of a fantastic book ,"[('only cover half', 'CARDINAL')]"
22034,"hbos ""game change"" wins best miniseries or motion picture made for television at the ",[]
22043,this feels like the start of a drinking game drink everything wins something ,[]
22099,game change wins for best miniseries tv movie ,[]
22139,game change wins for best miniseries or tv movie zero people are surprised ,"[('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
22142,the hour should have won ,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]"
22151,so who won the award for being the best child of a celebrity ,[]
22155,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
22157,rt @washingtonpost wins best miniseries or tv movie ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
22199,hatfields and mccoys should have won that boo ,[]
22224,yoshiki wins special award for cutest guy at the golden globes,[]
22240,not only did i fall asleep and miss the game yuck patriots win but we both forgot about the golden globes and missed the red carpet,[]
22307,yah idk whats really going on with the golden globes but if leo doesnt win best male actor in a predominantly gay role then there is no god,[]
22326,"""@thewrap golden globes 2013 christoph waltz wins best supporting actor ","[('2013', 'DATE')]"
22349,rt @nathanfillion en route to golden globes hope i win ,[]
22378,political animals deserved to win like seriously its the best show ,[]
22388,of course christoph waltz wins for best supp actor of course ,[]
22397,yup of course the hour wouldnt win in america but ugh its so amazing ,"[('the hour', 'TIME'), ('america', 'GPE')]"
22404, wins no way shouldve been ,[]
22405,did anyone think wasnt going to win ps loved the girl,"[('ps', 'ORG')]"
22415,rt @qtarchives and the winner is christoph waltz django unchained ,[]
22436, game change wins best mini series tv movie,[]
22437,rt @tvguide and the winner for best miniseries or tv movie goes to game change ,[]
22439,liked game change just won gg but liked hatfields and mccoys much better ,[]
22444,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
22451,saw the game change win a mile off expect harris moore to win too and rightfully so you betcha ,"[('a mile', 'QUANTITY'), ('harris moore', 'PERSON')]"
22453,game change wins best tv movie ,[]
22463,rt @ditzkoff i assume this is maggie smiths reaction to her golden globes win ,"[('rt @ditzkoff', 'PERSON')]"
22464,"""game change"" wins the for best tv movie or miniseries ",[]
22474,so glad won ,[]
22483,yeah maggie smith won best actress for her role on downton abbey i love her ,"[('downton abbey', 'PERSON')]"
22527,congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,[]
22536,the table setup would drive me insane if i won an award speech from my chair ,[]
22541,they already won the emmy and the hour was clearly the best choice up there ,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]"
22553,game change wins best miniseries what a deserving win ,[]
22556,@lenadunham is just too damn cute and she hasnt even won yet ,[]
22621,yay maggie smith for the win i love that woman outstanding actress god bless the brits ,"[('god', 'PERSON')]"
22623,the antisarah palin movie wins the imagine my surprise,"[('the antisarah palin', 'ORG')]"
22624,rt @hggirlonfire game change with woody harrelson wins best miniseries ,[]
22640,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
22642,game change wins best miniseries or tv movie ,[]
22724, won i was an in that movie,[]
22746,rt @vanityfair maggie smith as predicted wins supporting actress in tv for @downtonabbey sadly she is not at the to make a speech,"[('rt @vanityfair', 'ORG'), ('smith', 'ORG'), ('@downtonabbey', 'ORG')]"
22752,yesss game change won loved that movie ,[]
22765,rt @ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj,"[('@ap', 'ORG')]"
22767,definitely expecting anne hathaway to give her princess diaries speech if she wins tonight ,"[('anne hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
22799,rt @meanchelled yes maggie smith is always the best part of downton and any award that doesnt go to modern family is a win for everyone ,"[('maggie smith', 'PERSON'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
22802,game change wins best tv mini seriesdrama ,[]
22822,rt @nbc christoph waltz wins the award for best supporting actor in a motion picture for his role in django unchained ,[]
22853,game change wins best tv movieminiseries definitely not surprised ,[]
22866,rt @ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj,"[('@ap', 'ORG')]"
22903,game change wins the which officially makes it the only thing mccainpalin 2012 ever won,"[('2012', 'DATE')]"
22905,"seems like that movie ran years ago ""game change"" the sarah palin thing wins best tv movie ","[('years ago', 'DATE'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
22906,so happy that won @goldenglobes,[]
22911," wow@hbos ""game change"" just won via @youtube",[]
22930,so happy that won im a big fan ,[]
22936,rt @hollywoodlegacy golden globe classics on the red carpet of 1962 where she received an honorary award ,"[('rt @hollywoodlegacy golden globe classics', 'ORG'), ('1962', 'DATE')]"
22960,the hour should have won ,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]"
22965,first upset of the night hatfields and mc coys did not win for best mini series,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
22966,omg congrats danny strong andrew won a golden globe ,"[('omg congrats danny strong', 'PERSON'), ('andrew', 'PERSON')]"
22974,@katiecouric game change won for best mini series or tv movie ,"[('@katiecouric', 'ORG')]"
22991,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
22997,if your show is on hbo you automatically have a higher chance to winthey win everything lol ,[]
23000,game change wins the golden globes its official john mccain is the only person sarah palin hasnt brought success to ,"[('john mccain', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23011,"""@ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj"" the dr @jermainemoore88","[('the dr @jermainemoore88', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
23051,pretty pleased with the wins so far especially dame maggie smith wouldve liked to have seen the hour win ,[]
23066,somewhere sarah palin is trying to take credit for the win ,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23097,great movie game change wins best miniseries or tv movie ,[]
23101,@carycheyennexo i am really liking kate hudson and i agree about hayden but i knew maggie smith would win,"[('@carycheyennexo', 'ORG')]"
23131,thrilled that professor mcgonnagall won that is what she was nominated for right ,[]
23160,rt @bookishbelle the best miniseries or tv movie winner is game change ,"[('rt @bookishbelle', 'ORG')]"
23176,"""@keithurban whos watching the me just waiting to see you win ","[('@keithurban', 'ORG')]"
23232,the hour should have won because dominic west ,"[('the hour', 'TIME')]"
23235,woo hoo @juliannemoores game change wins best mini series or tv movie ,"[('woo hoo @juliannemoores game', 'ORG')]"
23247,glad to see game change win for one i saw it but it was well done too ,[]
23258,rt @naturallysteph jonathan from buffy i love it when he wins awards ,"[('rt @naturallysteph jonathan', 'PERSON')]"
23261, there for win for ,[]
23291,impresso minha ou esto treinando a jennifer lawrence pra ser a nova beard do nosso amigo victor garbers bottom bitch ,"[('jennifer lawrence', 'PERSON')]"
23315,rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('@masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'ORG')]"
23327,love game change so deserving pulling for julianne moore to win next ,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
23337,political animals should have won that show was amazing but i love julianne moore so its acceptable ,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
23354,so glad that won sad that @realsigourney didnt win for ,"[('@realsigourney', 'PERSON')]"
23374,"rt @ijasonyu ""@jjonz100 maggie smith didnt think shed win so shes at chuck e cheese"" no @theladygrantham is at downton arbys ","[('chuck', 'PERSON'), ('@theladygrantham', 'ORG'), ('downton', 'GPE')]"
23393,rt @alecmapa i love that the movie about sarah palin has long won more elections than sarah palin,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23398,still always laugh thinking about danny strong on when he wins everything is nominated for ,[]
23401,anyone surprised that won in liberal hollywood ,[]
23407,rt @alecmapa i love that the movie about sarah palin has long won more elections than sarah palin,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23421,why do people look so confused and the team scattered when they win ,[]
23438,yayyy my favorite from @hbo won the from @goldenglobes,[]
23486,rt @laceyvrose in an utterly unsurprising twist hbos wins for best miniseries or tv movie ,"[('rt @laceyvrose', 'PERSON')]"
23529,@goldenglobes sofia vergara did not win,"[('@goldenglobes sofia vergara', 'ORG')]"
23531,what the hell is this hbo show that just won on ive never heard of this crap but julianne moore is in it so,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
23544,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
23580,its a fair trade off the wife watched the falcons win earlier now i take in the golden globes,[]
23586,its the first day of the australian open sharapova opens with a big win over puchkova also the golden globes has started,"[('the first day', 'DATE'), ('australian', 'NORP'), ('puchkova', 'ORG')]"
23606,rt @tvwithoutpity once again thanks to danny strong were going to consider a win for to be a win for buffy ok ,[]
23607,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
23625, wins best miniseries or tv movie ,[]
23633,game change was so well done glad it won the gg for best tv movie ,[]
23645,like a fine wine even better with age maggie smith wins for still up for her role in quartet ,[]
23647,rt @ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj,"[('@ap', 'ORG')]"
23664,the make me hate hbo more and more every year any show on that network wins everything,[]
23671,having a speech prepared when you win an award is just like a middle finger to the other nominees ,[]
23675,rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations maggie smith on your win for ,"[('rt @pbs rt @masterpiecepbs congratulations', 'PERSON')]"
23686,rt @smhentnews first comedy now sarah palin is now the dramatic gift that keeps on giving after game change win ,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23695,rt @ladyantebellum been fighting my wife on tv decisions nfl playoffs and guess who won will somebody tell me who won the game ck,[]
23702,rt @vanityfair maggie smith as predicted wins supporting actress in tv for @downtonabbey sadly she is not at the to make a speech,"[('rt @vanityfair', 'ORG'), ('smith', 'ORG'), ('@downtonabbey', 'ORG')]"
23735,a win for game change well deserved you betcha ,[]
23745,if anyone is gonna win for nashville its connie britton ,"[('britton', 'ORG')]"
23794,@chels725 @goldenglobes i know this is silly but i like to think that the winners are decided moments before they actually win,[]
23796,rt @alecmapa i love that the movie about sarah palin has long won more elections than sarah palin,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
23802,confused as to why the music after the winner is announced sounds like the theyre walking to their death @ahoner,[]
23803,"i have never watched a tv movie or miniseries oh wait i did watch ""project alf"" it didnt win a it was robbed",[]
23869,congrats to christoph waltz maggie smith and game change on their wins ,"[('smith', 'ORG')]"
23884,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
23895,the fact that people win awards making fun of republicans should tell the gop to just go the fuck home ,"[('republicans', 'NORP'), ('gop', 'ORG')]"
23924,rt @rallisp christoph waltz wins best supporting actor for django unchained great actor great movie ,[]
23943,take off an article of clothing any time maggie smith wins ,[]
23956,i was really hoping hatfieldsmccoys was gonna win ,[]
23957,could care less who wins the awards just like all the other stuff ,[]
23975,rt @vanityfair maggie smith as predicted wins supporting actress in tv for @downtonabbey sadly she is not at the to make a speech,"[('rt @vanityfair', 'ORG'), ('smith', 'ORG'), ('@downtonabbey', 'ORG')]"
23993,so glad christoph waltz won he was brilliant in django unchained ,[]
23998,is maggie smith too old to travel to america or what she never comes but always wins ,"[('america', 'GPE')]"
24000, so glad she won rt @thr maggie smith wins the golden globe for best supporting cont ,"[('smith', 'PERSON')]"
24002,i truly believe leo dicaprio has been blackballed by the hollywood awardsfilm industry he is a fantastic actor never wins ,[]
24007,"""christopher waltz won a previous golden globe for his role as a violent antisemite a role made famous by mel gibson"" ","[('christopher waltz', 'PERSON'), ('mel gibson', 'PERSON')]"
24009,rt @ap christoph waltz wins golden globe for best supporting actor rjj,"[('@ap', 'ORG')]"
24026,rt @mugglenet congratulations to dame maggie smith for her golden globe win as best supporting actress in a tv series ,"[('rt @mugglenet congratulations', 'ORG')]"
24029,disappointed that sofia vergara never wins seriously whats up with that ,[]
24035,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
24040,rt @vulture maggie smith wins best supporting actress in a tv show everyone playing tina and amys drinking game bottoms up ,"[('tina', 'GPE'), ('amys', 'GPE')]"
24072,si los fuesen en venezuela el fashion police lo haria el tierrudo de la hojilla como se llama el won ese,"[('los fuesen', 'GPE'), ('venezuela el', 'GPE'), ('haria el tierrudo de la', 'PERSON'), ('llama el won ese', 'ORG')]"
24074,rt @washingtonpost wins best miniseries or tv movie ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON')]"
24104,every time leonardo dicaprio doesnt win an award he is nominated for a little piece of my heart breaks top 5 favorite actor ,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
24119,rt @etonlinealert game change wins best tv movie et has all the coverage ,"[('rt @etonlinealert', 'PERSON')]"
24123,rt @mharrisperry game change wins i kind of love that ,[]
24127,when a winner is announced i think exciting music should be played to encourage livelier stage entrance ,[]
24132,rt @downtonthehatch drink whenever maggie smith wins award but cant be bothered to fly to the colonies to retrieve it ,[]
24148,the little nerd from gilmore girls won another award for game change ,[]
24178,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
24179,"rt @morocca ""and the winner is maggie smith maggie smith couldnt give a sh we accept this award on her behalf"" ","[('rt @morocca ""', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'ORG')]"
24181,rt @kelseylmoore i want to win all of the becuz its the only movie i saw ashamed but not cuz it was so good,[]
24185,rt @washingtonpost maggie smith wins best supporting actress for tv performance in abbey ,"[('rt @washingtonpost', 'PERSON'), ('smith', 'PERSON')]"
24193,"who thinks ""life of pi"" will win it ",[]
24200,obv game change was going to win that but political animals was so good i was devastated when they opted out of season 2 ,"[('season 2', 'DATE')]"
24231,golden globes no need to take a poke at sarah palin when game change just won a statuett,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
24258,rt @ditzkoff i assume this is maggie smiths reaction to her golden globes win ,"[('rt @ditzkoff', 'PERSON')]"
24267,rt @huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at ,"[('@huffingtonpost', 'ORG')]"
24280,gee im shocked that a propaganda film like game change won the golden globes simply shocked ,[]
24292,queen lange for the win ,[]
24303,has won anything cc @onlyamikki ,[]
24317,i hope jessica lange wins ,"[('jessica', 'PERSON')]"
24320,lange will win ,[]
24327,jessica lange you lovely woman i hope you win ,"[('jessica', 'PERSON')]"
24342,rt @bbcnewsus dame wins at best supporting actress in a tv movie series or miniseries for ,"[('rt @bbcnewsus', 'PERSON')]"
24350,rt @theatlanticwire game change wins best tv miniseriesmovie jay roach gets in there with a very timely sarah palin dig ,"[('jay roach', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
24383,rt @alecmapa i love that the movie about sarah palin has long won more elections than sarah palin,"[('sarah palin', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
24391,"""sigourney weaver couldnt be here tonight because she didnt win"" ","[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
24395,a huge congratulations to on her win for abbey ,[]
24418,if jessica lange doesnt win we riot ,"[('jessica', 'PERSON')]"
24426,rt @vanityfair game change continues its emmy winning streak with first win julianne moore continues her flawless streak at podium,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
24448,"rt @imkristenbell here here ""@daxshepard1 in the unlikely event cooper doesnt win i hope security has a plan in place ","[('rt @imkristenbell', 'PERSON')]"
24451,"of course ""game change"" win at make fun of republicans win an award in hollywood even if your movie is crap","[('republicans', 'NORP')]"
24462,rooting for jessica lange if she doesnt win im jumping out of my window ,"[('jessica', 'PERSON')]"
24483,cant believe the hatfields mccoys didnt win for best mini series ,[]
24485,@adenamaria maggie smith won best supporting actress for on the ,[]
24500,rt @mjfanclub flashback to 1973 where michael jackson attended the and won best original song for ben ,"[('1973', 'DATE'), ('michael jackson', 'PERSON'), ('ben', 'PERSON')]"
24501,rt @bekywinkler christoph waltz was too incredible not to win best performance of the year period ,"[('@bekywinkler', 'ORG'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
24561,best actress in tv film or miniseries winner isjulianne moore for game change ,[]
24583,im only watching cause i want ahs to win something,[]
24620,jessica lange should have won ,"[('jessica', 'PERSON')]"
24621,does everyone have to get on stage when their movie wins at theyre going to miss the fruit cup,[]
24626,dang u typed that fast lol rt @aggiashagre game change starring julianne moore wins best miniseries or tv movie category ,"[('dang', 'ORG'), ('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
24628,rt @bbcnewsus dame wins at best supporting actress in a tv movie series or miniseries for ,"[('rt @bbcnewsus', 'PERSON')]"
24676, jessica lange you won in my heart,[]
24698, didnt win what ,[]
24749,best actress in a miniseries or tv movie winner is julianne moore game change ,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
24761, awww never won whatever,[]
24776,julianne wins not because she was the best but because everyone hates sarah palin ,"[('julianne', 'PERSON'), ('sarah palin', 'PERSON')]"
24789,another predictable and welldeserved win for julianne moore ,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
24792,"""@huffingtonpost christoph waltz wins best supporting actor at as he should have",[]
24848,"rt @thr ""game change"" wins the for best tv movie or miniseries ","[('rt @thr ""', 'PERSON')]"
24868,rt @cosmopolitan amy poehlers cleavage for the double win tonight ,"[('@cosmopolitan', 'GPE'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
24890,rt @goldenglobes here we go the 70th @goldenglobes starts now follow along for exclusive updates winner announcements and live tweets ,"[('70th', 'ORDINAL')]"
24913,julianne moore wins for ,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
24943,"""mjfanclub flashback to 1973 where michael jackson attended the and won best original song for ben ","[('1973', 'DATE'), ('michael jackson', 'PERSON'), ('ben', 'PERSON')]"
24966,woot woot for julianne moore i wanna watch that movie again tonight for the win,"[('julianne moore', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
24974,rt @vanityfair game change continues its emmy winning streak with first win julianne moore continues her flawless streak at podium,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('julianne moore', 'PERSON')]"
